{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question": "Who played the iconic doll Chucky, in the Child's Play (1988)?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "Brad Dourif",
                "wrong answer1": "Chris Sarandon",
                "wrong answer2": "Gary Oldman",
                "wrong answer3": "John Morghen"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question": " What kind of drink did R.J. MacReady often have in his hand in The Thing (1982)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Bourbon",
                "right answer": "Whiskey",
                "wrong answer2": "Apple Juice",
                "wrong answer3": "Vodka"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "Which Oscar nominated actor/actress did his/her film debut in A Nightmare on Elm Street (1984)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Naomi Watts",
                "right answer": "Johnny Depp",
                "wrong answer2": "Laura Linney",
                "wrong answer3": "Brad Pitt"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": " In how many movies did Kane Hodder play Jason Voorhees in the Friday the 13th series?",
            "answers": {
            	"wrong answer1": "6",
                "wrong answer2": "2",
                "wrong answer3": "3",
                "right answer": "4"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "Which movie was Oscar winning director Peter Jackson's directorial debut?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "They Live",
                "wrong answer2": "Braindead(Dead Alive)",
                "right answer": "Bad Taste",
                "wrong answer3": "Basket Case"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question": "Who directed the movie based on the Stephen King novel Christine in 1983?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "John Carpenter",
                "wrong answer1": "Stuart Gordon",
                "wrong answer2": "Wes Craven",
                "wrong answer3": "Sam Raimi"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question": "Who did most the creature effects in The Thing (1982)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Tom Savini",
                "wrong answer2": "Greg Nicatero",
                "right answer": "Rob Bottin",
                "wrong answer3": "Stan Winston"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question": "Who played the deranged scientist Herbert West in the Re-Animator trilogy?",
            "answers": {
           	 	"wrong answer1": "Bruce Campbell",
                "right answer": "Jeffrey Combs",
                "wrong answer2": "Donald O'brian",
                "wrong answer3": "Brad Dourif"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question": "Who played Dr. Butcher in Zombie Holocaust (1980)?",
            "answers": {
            	"wrong answer1": "John Morghen",
            	"wrong answer2": "Christopher George",
                "wrong answer3": "David Warbeck",
                "right answer": "Donald O'brian"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question": "From who's short story was From Beyond (1986) based?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "H.P. Lovecraft",
                "wrong answer1": "Stephen King",
                "wrong answer2": "Edgar Allan Poe",
                "wrong answer3": "Dean Koontz"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "11",
            "question": "Which director made his film debut with The Evil Dead (1981)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Wes Craven",
                "wrong answer2": "Sean S.Cunningham",
                "right answer": "Sam Raimi",
                "wrong answer3": "Stuart Gordon"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "12",
            "question": "What was the name of Danny's imaginary friend in The Shining (1980)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Eddy",
                "right answer": "Tony",
                "wrong answer2": "Johnny",
                "wrong answer3": "Kenny"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "13",
            "question": "In Gremlins (1984) Kate (Phoebe Cates) talks about a bad childhood memory in which she and her mother finds something horrible in their chimney. What did they find?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "Her dead father in a santa suit",
                "wrong answer1": "A gremlin in a santa suit",
                "wrong answer2": "A nest of dead crows",
                "wrong answer3": "Their long lost dog hanging dead in their christmas lights"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "14",
            "question": "In Pumpkinhead (1988), why does Ed Harley want to take revenge on a bunch of teenagers?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "They were toying with a gun and accidentally shoot and kill his brother",
                "wrong answer2": "They accidentally crash into his wife's car, killing her",
                "wrong answer3": "They rob his store and in the process accidentally shoot and kill his daughter",
                "right answer": "They accidentally ran over and killed his son"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "15",
            "question": "From what movie: 'We have such sights to show you!'?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Re-Animator",
                "right answer": "Hellraiser",
                "wrong answer2": "Warlock",
                "wrong answer3": "Evil Dead 2: Dead by Dawn"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "16",
            "question": "What was the reason for the creatures in Humanoids from the Deep (1980)?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "They come from space",
                "wrong answer2": "A mad scientist splicing man and fish",
                "right answer": "An experiment on fish gone awry",
                "wrong answer3": "They're an ancient species unleashed from the deep"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "17",
            "question": "From what movie: 'You say you hate Washington's Birthday or Thanksgiving and nobody cares but you say you hate Christmas and people treat you like you're a leper.'?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Elves",
                "right answer": "Gremlins",
                "wrong answer2": "Silent Night, Deadly Night",
                "wrong answer3": "Christmas Evil"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "18",
            "question": "What kind of animal bit of part of Jennifer Connely's finger during the filming of Phenomena (1985)?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "A chimpanzee",
                "wrong answer1": "A dog",
                "wrong answer2": "A crokodile",
                "wrong answer3": "A rat"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "19",
            "question": "In Killer Klowns from Outer Space (1988), What did the killer clowns use to wrap their victims in?",
            "answers": {
                "right answer": "Cotton candy",
                "wrong answer1": "Wrapping paper",
                "wrong answer2": "Green slime",
                "wrong answer3": "popcorn"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "20",
            "question": "In Maniac (1980), what part of his victims does the killer take and nail to his manikins?",
            "answers": {
                "wrong answer1": "Their hands",
                "wrong answer2": "Their skins",
                "wrong answer3": "Their heads",
                "right answer": "Their scalps"
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "21",
            "question": "Who directed City of the Living Dead (1980)?",
            "answers": {
            	"wrong answer1": "Dario Argento",
                "right answer": "Lucio Fulci",
                "wrong answer2": "Ruggero Deodato",
                "wrong answer3": "Bruno Mattei"
            }
        }
    ]
}